Voicebits

Privacy Policy
--------------

This Policy explains when and why we collect personal information about people who visit our website or web application, how we use it, the conditions under which we may disclose it to others and how we keep it secure.

We may change this policy from time to time so please check this page occasionally to ensure that you’re happy with any changes. By using our website or web application, you’re agreeing to be bound by this policy. Where possible we will notify you of any changes of policy within Voicebits.co.

Any questions regarding this policy and our privacy practices should be sent by email to [hello@voicebits.co](mailto:hello@voicebits.co).

What personal data do we collect?
---------------------------------

**Personal Data You Provide to Us Voluntarily** – We collect information about you that you voluntarily provide to us when you: (i) contact us to learn more about Voicebits.co, Subscribe to a mailing list or other opportunities you indicate are of interest at the time; (ii) access or use Voicebits.co's Services; or (iii) contact customer service. This information may include, for example, your name, business name, and any other information that you choose to provide to us when you comment on materials on our Voicebits.co Services, in order to contact you as a potential customer, or respond to a support request. This also includes technical data, such as IP addresses and device identifiers that are commonly generated in establishing a connection with the Voicebits.co Services. Payment information collected is processed securely by our Payment processor and is not stored in Voicebits.co's databases. This is bound by our processor's privacy policy and will not be passed on to third parties under any circumstances.

**Retention** - We collect and retain Personal Data submitted to Voicebits.co in an identifiable format for the amount of time necessary to meet your request or fulfil our legal or regulatory obligations, unless it is in our legitimate business interests and not prohibited by law to maintain the Personal Data for longer periods.

**Other Data** - By using the Voicebits.co services we may store information about what pages have been visited and when. This is to help us improve the usability of our services.

How do we process personal data?
--------------------------------

We may use information for our legitimate interests, namely:

* To operate the Voicebits.co Services.
* To contact and communicate with you when you reach out to us to ask us about our Voicebits.co Services.
* To manage everyday business needs.
* To analyze or improve the Voicebits.co Services or additional products or services.
* To protect the Voicebits.co Services and the rights of Users and others to enforce the terms of the Voicebits.co Services.
* To comply with our obligations, including to comply with all applicable laws and regulations.

Who has access to your information?
-----------------------------------

Under no circumstances will we directly disclose or sell your personal information to any third party. We are strongly against any form of internet 'spam' and keep all collected information strictly confidential in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR).

We will not sell or provide your information to third parties for marketing purposes.

Security and your data
----------------------

We take data security very seriously. Our databases are backed up regularly, and any data collected from you is sent over an encrypted SSL secure connection. Security of our data is important to us and we take every possible reasonable measure to prevent against loss, damage, theft or misuse where possible.

Links to other websites
-----------------------

Our website, help centre and web application may contain links to other websites run by other organisations. This privacy policy applies only to our services‚ so we encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit. We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other sites even if you access them using links from our website. In addition, if you linked to our website from a third party site, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of the owners and operators of that third party site and recommend that you check the policy of that third party site.

Legal
-----

All customer data is handled sensitively by members of our team and physical access to our offices is restricted to authorised personnel only.

Voicebits.co reserves the right to make alterations to this document whenever we deem reasonable. It is the client's sole responsibility to check this document for updates on a regular basis.

Your rights
-----------

If at any point you believe the information we process on you is incorrect you can request to see this information and even have it corrected or deleted.

Please be aware, in order to remove any of your data this may prevent us from providing services to you and could result in the closure of your account.

If you have any concerns regarding the data we hold on you, please contact us at [hello@voicebits.co](mailto:hello@voicebits.co).
